export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your overall mood on a typical day?",
      "options": [
        "Generally positive",
        "Neutral",
        "Occasionally sad",
        "Frequently sad or low"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Generally positive"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you often experience feelings of hopelessness or helplessness?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely or never",
        "Occasionally",
        "Frequently",
        "Almost always"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely or never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you noticed changes in your appetite, either overeating or loss of appetite?",
      "options": [
        "No changes",
        "Increased appetite",
        "Decreased appetite",
        "Fluctuations between increased and decreased appetite"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No changes"
    },
    {
      "question": "How is your sleep pattern affected? Do you experience difficulty sleeping or oversleeping?",
      "options": [
        "No sleep issues",
        "Difficulty sleeping",
        "Oversleeping",
        "Fluctuations between difficulty and oversleeping"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No sleep issues"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you often feel fatigued or lacking in energy?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely or never",
        "Occasionally",
        "Frequently",
        "Almost always"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely or never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you lost interest or pleasure in activities that you used to enjoy?",
      "options": [
        "No loss of interest",
        "Occasional loss of interest",
        "Frequent loss of interest",
        "Complete loss of interest"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No loss of interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with depression?",
      "options": [
        "Yes",
        "Considering it",
        "No, not yet",
        "No, and I don't plan to"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you find it challenging to concentrate or make decisions?",
      "options": [
        "No challenges",
        "Slight challenges",
        "Moderate challenges",
        "Severe challenges"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No challenges"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you experienced a persistent feeling of sadness or emptiness?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely or never",
        "Occasionally",
        "Frequently",
        "Almost always"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely or never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing mood and emotional well-being is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree",
        "Agree",
        "Neutral",
        "Disagree"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    }
  ]
}
